otaquest.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy – OTAQUEST

* * *

Last modified: June 1, 2019

**_Introduction_**

LDH JAPAN Inc. ( **“Company”** or **“We”** ) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website _https://www.otaquest.com_ (our “ **Website** “) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

● On this Website.

● In email, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

● Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or

● Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see _Changes to Our Privacy Policy_ ). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**_Children Under the Age of 13_**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [contact@otaquest.com](mailto:contact@otaquest.com).

**  
_Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It_  
**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

● By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, payment card information or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“ **personal information** “);

● That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as gender, age, interests and recent and upcoming purchases; and/or

● About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:

● Directly from you when you provide it to us.

● Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies.

**_Information You Provide to Us_**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

● Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering with our Website, making a purchase on our Website and subscribing to our newsletters. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.

● Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.

● Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research, marketing and product development purposes.

● Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.

● Your search queries on the Website.

**_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

● Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.

● Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

Our Website does not look for or respond to “do not track” signals.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

● Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

● Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.

● Speed up your searches.

● Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

● **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.

**_Third-Party Use of Cookies_**

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this Website. Google Analytics collect information regarding your use of other websites and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/, and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**_How We Use Your Information_**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

● To present our Website and its contents to you.

● To process and fulfill your order, including by shipping products to you, or others you designate, and sending emails to you, or others you designate, to confirm your order status and shipment and to process merchandise returns.

● To provide you with after-sales services.

● To communicate with you and send you information about products, services, promotions, special offers and web contents.

● To send newsletters to subscribers.

● To provide you with other information, products, or services that you request from us.

● To address problems with and improve our products, brands and services as well as to develop new products and services.

● To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

● To provide you with notices about your account/subscription.

● To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.

● To prevent, detect, mitigate and investigate fraud, security breaches and  
activities that are or potentially may be prohibited or illegal.

● To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we  
offer or provide though it.

● In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

● For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please [check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the [order form/registration form])/adjust your user preferences in your account profile.] For more information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**_Disclosure of Your Information_**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

● To our subsidiaries and affiliates.

● To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.

● To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

● To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.

● For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

● With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

● To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

● To enforce or apply our Website Terms and Use or Online Sale Terms and Conditions and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

● If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of COMPANY, our customers, or others.

**  
_Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_  
**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

● **Cookies** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

● **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by [[checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the [order form/registration form])/[OTHER OPT-OUT METHOD]] or at any other time by] [logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by] sending us an email stating your request to [contact@otaquest.com](mailto:contact@otaquest.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, product service experience or other transactions.

● **Google Analytics**. You can opt out of Google Analytics’ cookies by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**_Accessing and Correcting Your Information_**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account page.

You may also send us an email at [contact@otaquest.com](mailto:contact@otaquest.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

**_Your California Privacy Rights_**

California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [contact@otaquest.com](mailto:contact@otaquest.com)

**_Data Security_**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy without prior notice to you. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**_Contact Information_**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at [contact@otaquest.com](mailto:contact@otaquest.com)
